ANKIT PRAJAPATI

+1(437)665-2829

ankit8620prajapati@gmail.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/ankit-prajapati-435953219 Oshawa, ON

Energetic Customer Service Representative with experience resolving complex customer inquiries and managing sales results. Passionate about building strong customer relationships, driving brand loyalty, and increasing customer engagement. Excellent communication skills, great analytical skills and ability to work precisely in any driven environment.

WORK EXPERIENCE

FULL TIME:

BUSINESS DEVELOPMENT INTERN

Atigo Electronics India Pvt Ltd, INDIA

August 2023 - November 2023

- Conducted market research to identify new business opportunities and expand the customer base.
- Assisted in the development of sales strategies to target potential markets.
- Collaborated with cross-functional teams to drive sales and ensure client satisfaction.
- Analyzed sales data to provide insights and recommendations for business growth.
- Generated leads and maintained client relationships, resulting in a 15% increase in sales.

SALES MANAGEMENT INTERN

K. J. Jewellers

July 2022 - March 2023

- Assisted in managing daily sales operations, including inventory management and customer service.
- Developed sales presentations and marketing strategies to increase product visibility.
- Trained and mentored new employees on sales techniques and customer service.
- Spearheaded promotional campaigns that resulted in a 10% revenue increase during key sales periods.
- Handled customer inquiries and complaints to ensure positive shopping experiences.

SALES MANAGEMENT INTERN

Brahmani Cutlery and Stationery General Store

April 2019 - June 2022

- Managed product inventory and implemented efficient stock control measures.
- Provided exceptional customer service and resolved product-related queries.
- Processed cash, credit card transactions, and handled cash management.
- Assisted in product promotions and upselling, contributing to a 12% increase in sales.
- Collaborated with the team to ensure smooth day-to-day operations.

PART TIME:

CUSTOMER SERVICE REPRESENTATIVE & SANDWICH ARTIST

Subway

December 2023 - March 2024

- Crew member exhibits a cheerful and helpful manner while greeting guests and preparing their orders.
- Demonstrates a complete understanding of menu items and explains them to guests accurately.
- To resolve the complaint by the customer and provide an appropriate solution. Uses Point of Sale system/cash register (cashier) to record the order and compute the

- amount of the bill. Collects payment from guests and returns proper change amount.
- Performs Cash-In Procedure- accounting for all forms of money, bread, etc., during the shift.
- Prepares food neatly, according to formula, and in a timely manner.

SKILLS:

- Customer Service
- Cash Handling
- Inventory Management
- Point of Sale

- Problem Solving
- CRM Software
- Multi-tasking

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY:

BACHELOR OF BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION Gujarat University(July 2019- April 2022)

MARKETING MANAGEMENT
Georgian@ILAC college(Jan 2024- Aug 2024)

DATA ANALYTICS FOR BUSINESS DECISION MAKING Durham College(Sep 2024- Present)

REFERENCE:

• Available upon request